<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ARGame</string>
    <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="high_scores">High Scores</string>
    <string name="game_settings">Game Settings</string>
    <string name="resume_game">Resume Game</string>
    <string name="disable_tips">Disable Tips</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="default_username">Default username</string>
    <string name="description_avatar">A player avatar</string>
    <string name="games_played">Games played: </string>
    <string name="highest_score">Highest score: </string>
    <string name="choose_ability">Choose ability</string>
    <string name="select_abilities">Select abilities</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="next_level">Next Level</string>
    <string name="game_over">Game Over</string>
    <string name="level_completed">Level Completed!</string>
    <string name="btn_add">Add</string>
    <string name="btn_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="minus">-</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="create_new_user">Create new user</string>
    <string name="new_username">New username</string>
    <string name="score_username">Username:</string>
    <string name="score">Score:</string>
    <string name="tutorial_menu">
        The small x in the top right corner will open up a menu that
        provides an option to exit the game whenever you want.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial_abilities">
        The image buttons are abilities you can use to deal damage to the enemies, or protect yourself from them,
        and the numbers over them indicate that the ability is recharging before it may be used again.\nYou may have
        a maximum amount of four abilities at a time, and you\'re able to select your abilities
        each intermission between levels.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial_start_level">
        To be able to start the level, you must first let your camera find a horizontal plane.
        This may take some time depending on the environment. The optimal environment is somewhere
        light (preferable inside), and the optimal plane has some contrast.\nThe \"Start level\" button
        will light up when a plane is found, and pressing it — will begin the current level.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial_bars">
        The colored rectangular area above your head is your health bar.\nOnce the health bar turns completely black — you die.
        The black bar below the health bar is to keep track of your ultimate progress.\nUltimates are powerful abilities
        that you gain access to, after using a certain amount of regular abilities that progressively fill up the ultimate bar.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial_ults">
        The extra buttons between your regular abilities are your ultimate abilities. These buttons show up when your ultimate
        bar is full, and pressing either of them will enable a more powerful ability — that should be used in a tough situation.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial_killall">
        The ultimate on the left: \"Killall\", is an ultimate ability, that listens to your phone\'s internal acceleration sensor.\n
        Killall activates when you have moved your phone fast enough in any of it\'s axes. Once activated — will kill all enemies alive.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial_serenity">
        The ultimate on the right: \"Serenity\", is an ultimate ability, that listens to your phone\'s internal light sensor.\n
        To activate this ability — you have to either be in a dark place, or you have to place your hand over the sensor. 
        The light sensor usually looks like a small dot (like camera), and is usually located at the top of your phone, just above the screen.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
</resources>
